Finding Aid for Wilfred B. Shaw Papers 1873-1954
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs and other visual materials
  - Photograph Albums
    - Album of University of Michigan student activities, disbound circa 1900-1904
      - Fraternities and sororities
        - Delta Chi (Box 8)
        - Delta Gamma (Box 8)
        - Delta Kappa Epsilon (Box 8)
        - Delta Sigma Delta (Box 8)
        - Delta Tau Delta (Box 8)
        - Delta Upsilon (Box 8)
        - Gamma Phi Beta (Box 8)
        - Kappa Alpha Theta (Box 8)
        - Kappa Kappa Gamma (Box 8)
        - Kappa Sigma (Box 8)
        - Phi Chi (Box 8)
        - Phi Delta Phi (Box 8)
        - Phi Delta Theta (Box 8)
        - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 8)
        - Phi Kappa Psi (Box 8)
        - Pi Beta Phi (Box 8)
        - Psi Upsilon (Box 8)
        - Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 8)
        - Sigma Chi (Box 8)
        - Sigma Nu (Box 8)
        - Sigma Phi (Box 8)
        - Theta Delta Chi (Box 8)
        - Zeta Psi (Box 8)
      - Medicine, Nursing, and Dentistry (include hospital scenes) (Box 8)
      - Student organizations and other activities
        - Ann Arbor Golf Club grounds (Box 8)
        - Boating on Huron River (Box 8)
        - Comedy Club (Box 8)
        - Commencement procession (Box 8)
        - Literary Class Day under Tappan Oak 1903 (Box 8)
        - Michigamua (Box 8)
        - Southern Club (Box 8)
        - Union County Fair (Box 8)
        - U-M Orchestra (Box 8)
        - Western Club (Box 8)
      - Student rooms (Box 8)
  - Glass negatives
    - Nos. 1-41 (Box 7)
      (Numbers correspond to items listed in subsereies " copy prints from glass negatives")
      [staff use only]
  - Plates of etchings
    - Book plates, William H. Hobbs (Box 6)
      (no. 1)
    - Yakima Canyon (Box 6)
      (no. 2)
    - Unidentified man (Box 6)
      (no. 3)
    - Nude, zinc (Box 6)
      (no. 4)
    - Rest, nude (Box 6)
      (no. 5)
    - Seated nude, on celluloid (Box 6)
      (no. 6)
    - Seated nude (Box 6)
      (no. 7)
    - Boy Scout (Box 6)
      (no. 8)
    - The Burned Forest (Box 6)
      (no. 9)
    - Winter, drypoint (Box 6)
      (no. 10)
    - Bruges (Box 6)
      (no. 11)
    - On the Vinajanine (sic.) River (Box 6)
      (no. 12)
    - Heart of Paris (Box 6)
      (no. 13)
    - Shaw Christmas Card (Box 6)
      (no. 14)
    - Nude study, acid bitten (Box 6)
      (no. 15)
    - Unidentified street scene (Box 6)
      (no. 16)
    - Nude study (Box 6)
      (no. 17)
    - Aigler Residence, Ann Arbor (Box 6)
      (no. 18)
    - B.L. Shaw portrait (Box 6)
      (no. 19)
    - William L. Clements Building-Christmas card (Box 6)
      (no. 20)
    - 3 unidentified (Box 6)
      (no. 21)
    - Signs of spring-the Huron 1923 (Box 6)
      (no. 22)
    - The Thames, London (Box 6)
      (no. 23)
    - Thousand Islands (Box 6)
      (no. 24)
    - Keats grave (Box 6)
      (no. 25)
    - Picnic ground (Box 6)
      (no. 26)